<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Herd Manager</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Herds/Visits</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Options</string>
    <string name="title_activity_new_case">Add A New Herd</string>
    <string name="tutorial_text_farmer_management">
        If you don\'t see any farmers in your herd/visit view it means no farmer has been added yet.\n
        You can add a new farmer using the Add farmer button in the Add a New Herd page.\n
        You can use existing farmers by selecting Use Existing Farmer in the Add herd page.</string>

    <string name="tutorial_text_herd_management">
        To add a new herd click on the Add a New Herd on the main page.\n
        Before you can add a new herd you\'ll need to specify a herd size and assign a new or existing farmer to the herd.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_text_visit_management">
        To add a visit to a herd tap on herd/visits on the bottom bar.\n
        The page will show a list of all farmers, tap on the farmer\'s name to see herds belonging to the farmer.\n
        Click on add visit to add a new visit for the herd.\n\n
        At the top of the visit page you will see a tab with three sections : Herd Health, Herd Productivity and Herd Dynamics.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="tutorial_visit_herd_health">
        Herd Health\nYou can add disease and health sign information in health events.\nTo add a disease/sign tap on the add disease or add sign button.\nTo edit a disease/sign long tap on each disease or sign.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="tutorial_visit_herd_productivity">
         Herd Productivity\nYou can add information about pregnant animals and births, and information of milk production in productivity events.\nTo edit production information tap on the relevant edit button.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="tutorial_visit_herd_dynamics">
        Herd Dynamics\nHerd Dynamics contain information about animals bought,sold or lost.\n
        You can edit animal movement by clicking on the edit button.\n
        To add animal deaths tap on the add death button.\n
        To edit an animal death long tap on a specific animal death.\n
    </string>

    <string name="tutorial_text_sync_management">
        To sync your herd information with the server go to the options view.\n
        In the options view tap the sync button.\n
        The red circle beside each farmer\'s name will turn green if the farmer information has been synced.\n
        The red circle beside each farmers\'s name will turn blue if the farmer information has been partially synced.\n
        The red/blue/green circles are also shown beside each visit for the herd</string>


    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_herd_visit">AddHerdVisitActivity</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Herd\nHealth</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Herd\nProductivity</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">Herd\nDynamics</string>

</resources>
